翻译，时间轴，压制：Bolshevik0
这是一个关于时间的故事
It was about time...
Jeremy
Jeremy.
25年 我的生活仍如此平静
Twenty-five years and my life is still,
试着爬上这座巨大的希望之山
Trying to get up this great big hill of hope...
作为旅途的目的地
...for a destination.
我迅速地发现
I realized quickly when I knew I should,
世界是建立在人们的友情之上
that the world was made up of that brotherhood of man...
不管是什么事
...for whatever that means...
所以有时我躺在床上哭泣着
And so I cry sometimes when I'm lying in bed
只是为了搞清我到底在想什么
just to get it all out what's in my head and I...
我自己有些怪怪的
I'm feeling...a little peculiar.
我早上起来出去走走
So I wake in the morning and I step outside,
深呼吸一口 感到无比清爽
And I take a deep breath and I get real high and I...
用尽全力大声呼喊
...scream at the top of my lungs,
到底发生了什么
What's going on?
我说 嗨 嗨 嗨 嗨
And I say, hey hey hey hey
嗨 嗨 嗨
hey hey hey
我说 嗨
I said hey,
到底发生了什么
...what's going on?
我说 嗨 嗨 嗨 嗨
And I say, hey hey hey hey
嗨 嗨 嗨
hey hey hey
我说 嗨
I said hey,
到底发生了什么
...what's going on?
25年 我的生活仍如此平静
Twenty-five years and my life is still,
试着爬上这座巨大的希望之山
Trying to get up that great big hill of hope...
作为旅途的目的地
...for a destination...